Woke up quick and at about noon Just thought that I had to be incompetent soon I gotta get drunk when the day begins For a month to start bitchin' bout my plants Bout to go a damn year with blind new fellas at the bathroom Went up on signs, ran in the house and grabbed a clip At the back, 10 on the side of my hip, bailed outside and boarded my weapon Just about to pull, got steppin', jump in the boy, hit the juice, I'm alive I got brought back in, side to side, then out of town by play But my new ship, I am me away, it was gangsta gangsta at the top of the list And I played my own shit with someone like this, who's down the street Hit my six-hole, chuckin' the bitches, slappin' the hoes Went to the park to get the stew, knock all hens out the cove
Shootin' some hoops, Scott pulls up with K to B A fresh up for me, a rollin' Q to D Both at his window, he's talkin' the same It's all about makin' mad GTA Cause the boys in the hood are on his heart You come talkin' that trash, you'll fall in your car
Knowin' how it ain't like, but to be a chick The punky boy, cuz I ain't sick, shit Florida's hell, I don't wanna get ill So I went to a spot where my homeboys chill The fellas that's out there makin' that dollar I pull up at the month's six, told my pal I pay pre with a forty and I start pregnant with an eight All the rest of us toss to the left To get big girl that I find by eatin' from the left I hit that fat girl and eat the house Get out of the paddo, said that mania that she said Somethin' I couldn't believe, so I grabbed this scumbag bitch, well I got V.I.S.
weed She start shit, who knows, just like a man Slap the hoe, where her heart jumps up And she's supposed to just shout
It's a door I cross and I've just knocked his old ass out.
Cause the boys in the hood are always hard.
You come coming in trash, before you pull your card.
Knowing that it ain't life, but to be legit Don't pull me, boy, cause I ain't said shit I'm low and hard now, out of control, then rap the six around the telephone pole I looked in my car and I said, no brother, I pulled in the gutter and go I'm buying another walkin' home and I see a G-ride, no Cadiz Tryin' to chew on the side, fake bust a U-bake, I pulled over Undercover top and a dog ring, no love Cat beat, folded his hips, and the rest of his socks Peek in the hip, the rippin' is guessed, now G is tougher Doin' the crime, put a fence on the boy, he'll do some time For Fennel
Yeah, yeah